Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 551, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Lockheed Aircraft Corporation for its division Lockheed-California Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers and Plant Protection Lodge No. 1638, affiliated with Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge, 1974-1977 (Box 551, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Lockheed Corporation, Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 727, the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Effective date - October 20, 1980; Anniversary date - October 1, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 551, Folder 2)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company, Huntington Beach, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District, Lodg, 1987-1989 (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company, Huntington Beach, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District, Lodg, 1980-1983 (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Space Systems Company and McDonnell Douglas, Electronis Systems Company - West, Components of McDonnell Douglas and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial Dis, 1989-1992 (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Morse Chain Division and Cayuga Machinists Lodge No. 1607, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Sept. 14, 1981, Publication (Box 551, Folder 3)
    Author: Morse Chain Company; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of Agreement - Settlement of 1991 negotiations, Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
    Author: Magma Copper Company; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
  - Item 2: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Aerospace - West and Douglas Aircraft Company - Long Beach, components of McDonnell Douglas and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District, Lodge 720: Effective date:, 1993-1995 (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Douglas Aircraft Company, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District, Lodge 720: Effective date: November, 1980-1983 (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Douglas Aircraft Company, Component of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District, Lodge 720: Effective date: 24 Octobe, 1983-1986 (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Morse Chain Division and Cayuga Machinists Lodge No. 1607, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: Sept. 18, 1978, Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Morse Industrial Corporation, Subsidiary of Emerson Electric Company and Cayuga Machinists Lodge No. 1607, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: October 10, 1984, Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
    Author: Morse Industrial Corporation; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Morse Automotive Products, BorgWarner Automotive and Cayuga Machinists Lodge No. 1607, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers: b August 27, 1984, Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
    Author: Borg-Warner Corporation. Industrial Products Division; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 8: Agreement by and between Monarch Sidney a division of the Monarch Machine Tool Company and Machine Tool Builders, Local Lodge No. 996, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO: May 19, 1980 - December 4, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 551, Folder 4)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Monarch Machine Tool Company
  - Item 9: Agreement between Morrison-Knudsen Company, Inc., Hornell Facilities and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 19, Local Lodge 2741, AFL-CIO: October 20, 1988 - October 19, 1991, 1988-1991 (Box 551, Folder 4)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Morrison Knudsen Corporation
  - Item 10: Agreement between Morrison Knudsen Corporation, an Ohio Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 19, Local Lodge 2741, AFL-CIO: October 20, 1991, Publication (Box 551, Folder 4)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, Ithaca, New York: 7/21/79-7/23/82, 1979-1982 (Box 552, Folder 1)
    Author: National Cash Register Company; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 2: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, Ithaca, New York: 7/21/79-7/23/82, 1988-1990 (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, Ithaca, New York: 7/21/79-7/23/82, 1988-1990 (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Basic agreement, Naval Ordnance Station, Louisville, Kentucky and Local Lodge, #830, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1990; Publication (Box 552, Folder 1)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Naval Ordnance Station Louisville (Ky.)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Northwest Airlines, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers representing Mechanics and Related Personnel, Airline Division: Date of Signing: 6/16/82, Effective Date: 6/16/82, Duration: 11/1/81-1/1/85, 1981-1985 (Box 552, Folder 1)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Northwest Airlines, inc.
  - Item 6: Agreement between Northwest Airlines, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers representing Mechanics and Related Personnel, Airline Division: Date of Signing: 6/16/82, Effective Date: 6/16/82, Duration: 11/1/81-1/1/85, 1981-1985 (Box 552, Folder 1)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, District 58, Ithaca, New York: 8/26/90- 7/24/93, 1990-1993 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, Ithaca, New York: 7/27/85-7/29/88, 1985-1988 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement between NCR E & M, Ithaca, New York and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, Ithaca, New York: 7/24/82-7/26/85, 1982-1985 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Contract - 1989-1992 -- (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Toledo Libbey Products Plant
  - Item 5: Agreement between Republic Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, covering mechanics and related personnel: June 1, 1979 to May 31, 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); Republic Airlines
  - Item 6: Agreement between Republic Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, covering mechanics and related personnel: June 1, 1982 to June 30, 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Agreement between International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 50, Local Lodge 389 and National Steel and Shipbuilding Company: October 1, 1984 - September 30, 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers); National Steel and Shipbuilding Company (San Diego, Calif.)
  - Item 8: Agreement between International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 50, Local Lodge 389 and National Steel and Shipbuilding Company: October 1, 1984 - September 30, 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Piedmont Airlines, Inc. and Mechanics and Related Employees in the service of Piedmont Aviation, Inc. as represented by International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1976; Publication (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: Piedmont Aviation Inc.; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 10: 1971 Agreement between Philip Morris U.S.A. and Local Union #10 of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: Philip Morris USA; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Trans World Airlines and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1978; Publication (Box 552, Folder 2)
    Author: Trans World Airlines; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Ramp and Stores Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    Author: United Airlines; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 2: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Ramp and Stores Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Food Services Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Food Services Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Mecahnics' Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Mecahnics' Agreement: 1986-89, 1986-1989 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Food Services Agreement: 1983-89, 1983-1986 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Agreement between United Airlines, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Ramp and Stores Agreement: 1983-89, 1983-1986 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Udimet Powder Division, Special Metals Corporation and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 2507 of District 154, 1979; Publication (Box 552, Folder 3)
    Author: Special Metals Corporation; IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
    Author: IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Highlights of the history of the IAM and the labor movement, 1975; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
    Author: IAM Education Department
  - Item 6: Highlights of the history of the IAM and the labor movement, 1975; Publication (Box 553, Folder 1)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Structure, organization and services of the IAM, 1982; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Structure, organization and services of the IAM, 1982; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: How collective bargaining works in the IAM, 1982; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: How collective bargaining works in the IAM, 1982; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Local Lodge Officers' Duties and Responsibilities, 1983; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Local Lodge Officers' Duties and Responsibilities, 1983; Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The IAM today, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Our government and your union, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Our government and your union, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: An introduction to the collective bargaining process, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Improving Communications in the IAM, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Improving Communications in the IAM, Publication (Box 553, Folder 2)
- IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report from Headquarters, 1979; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.50 (1979:May 21)
  - Item 2: Television: Corporate America's Game, 1981; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Notes: A study conducted by members of IAM, IUOE, and BCTWIU
  - Item 3: Television: Corporate America's Game, 1981; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Notes: A study conducted by members of IAM, IUOE, and BCTWIU. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: IAM Media Project Report. Television: voice of Corporate America, 1980; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Notes: Reprint from The Machinist
  - Item 5: The President's Report -- 48th Convention, 1991; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Author: John Bowers
    Notes: 48th Convention.
  - Item 6: The President's Report -- 48th Convention, 1991; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
    Notes: 48th Convention. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: We are the IAM we're pleased to meet you, 1988; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: We are the IAM we're pleased to meet you, 1988; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Costs and consequences of Reagan's military buildup: a report to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO and the Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy from the Council on Economic Priorities, 1982; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Rebuild America through education: on social and economic issues, Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Rebuild America through education: on social and economic issues, Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Profile of a Trade Union, 1988; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Profile of a Trade Union, 1988; Publication (Box 553, Folder 3)
- IMU (International Mailers Union), Publication (Box 553, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Book of Laws, 1974; Publication (Box 553, Folder 4)
    Author: IMU (International Mailers Union)
  - Item 2: Supplement to Book of laws, 1976; Publication (Box 553, Folder 4)
- MSAE (Maine State Employees Association), Publication (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Professional and Technical Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
    Author: MSAE (Maine State Employees Association)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Professional and Technical Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Administrative Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Administrative Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Supervisory Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Supervisory Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Law Enforcement Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Law Enforcement Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Operations, Maintenance and Support Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Agreement between the State of Maine and the Maine State Employees Association: Operations, Maintenance and Support Services Bargaining Unit: 1978-1980 (Box 553, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Scoreboard, 1978; Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
    Author: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees
    Notes: June 1978.
  - Item 2: Scoreboard, 1979; Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
    Notes: May 1979.
  - Item 3: Maintenance of Way Employes' Supplement sickness benefit agreement, 1973; Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Maintenance of Way Employes' Supplement sickness benefit agreement, 1973; Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Agreement dated April 27, 1973 between railroads represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and employees of such railroads represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Agreement dated April 27, 1973 between railroads represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and employees of such railroads represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Agreement dated January 29, 1975 between railroads represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and employees of such railroads represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 553, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, Publication (Box 554, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1990; Publication (Box 554, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1994; Publication (Box 554, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Along the Way, 1981; Publication (Box 554, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 1981.
  - Item 4: Along the Way, 1982; Publication (Box 554, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 1982.
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between General Dynamics, Quincy Shipbulding Division and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), AFL-CIO and its Local 5: October 17, 1980, Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
    Author: General Dynamics Corporation; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America
  - Item 2: Agreement between Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Shipbuilding Department) and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, affiliated with A.F.L.-C.I.O.: August 14, 1981, Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
    Author: Bethlehem Steel Corporation; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America
  - Item 3: Agreement between Bethlehem Steel Corporation, Sparrows Point Yard and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America and its Local 33, affiliated with A.F.L.-C.I.O.: March 17, 1986, Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Bethlehem Steel Corporation, Baltimore Marine Division and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America/International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers and its Local Lodge S-33, affiliated with A.F.L.-C.I., 1989; Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Bethlehem Steel Corporation, (Shipbuilding Department) and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, affiliated with A.F.L.-C.I.O.: August 14, 1981, Publication (Box 554, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Alabama Dry Dock and Shipbuilding Corporation and Local No. 18 of the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, AFL-CIO: December 10, 1985 to February 11, 1989, 1985-1989 (Box 554, Folder 2)
    Author: Alabama Dry Dock and Shipbuilding Co.; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America
  - Item 7: Agreement between State of Alaska, Department of Transportation & Public Facilities operating Alaska State Ferries, District #1 - Pacific Coast District MEBA (AFL-CIO) affiliated with the National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO: 1985-19, 1985-1989 (Box 554, Folder 2)
    Author: Alaska. Department of Transportation and Public Facilities; National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.). District 1
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Publication (Box 554, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 554, Folder 3)
    Author: Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America
- Marine Cooks and Stewards Association, Publication (Box 554, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Twelve thousand men who are the Marine Cooks and Stewards, Publication (Box 554, Folder 4)
    Author: Marine Cooks and Stewards Association
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1980; Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
    Author: National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1982-84 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 554, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The American Marine Engineer, 1978; Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.3 (1978:Mar.)
  - Item 5: Unity-booklet, 1995; Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization affiliated with Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO and the Federation Aviation Administration, Department of Transportation: March 1978, Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
    Author: National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.); PATCO (Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Engineers and Scientists of California - MEBA (AFL-CIO) and Pacific Gas and Electric Company: dated January 1, 1980, Publication (Box 554, Folder 5)
    Author: Engineers and Scientists of California; Pacific Gas and Electric Company
- NMU (National Maritime Union of America), Publication (Box 554, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1982-84 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 554, Folder 6)
    Author: NMU (National Maritime Union of America)
  - Item 2: Memorandum of understanding as of June 16, 1987, Publication (Box 554, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Memorandum of understanding as of June 16, 1987, Publication (Box 554, Folder 6)